Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
TESSA:
Once upon a time
there was a girl named Tessa,
who had a dream.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Hey-ey-ey-ey ♪
♪ Workin' all day
Don't do a thing ♪
♪ Life's what you make it
You're in the driver's seat ♪
♪ Rev your engine
Crank the ignition ♪
♪ Give me the key
Don't need your permission ♪
♪ Momma always told me ♪
♪ There's nothin'
In this life to fear ♪
♪ You're gonna miss me
Zero to sixty ♪
♪ Kickin' it into gear ♪
♪ I'm in control
And behind the wheel ♪
♪ And I'm gonna steer
Where I want to steer ♪
♪ I'm in control
And behind the wheel ♪
♪ And I'm gonna steer
Where I'm gonna steer ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Go full throttle ♪
♪ Go full throttle, oh-oh ♪
♪ Pedal to the metal, oh-oh ♪
♪ Nothin' to see here ♪
♪ Get yourself in gear ♪
♪ And go full throttle ♪
♪ Go full throttle, oh-oh ♪
[CLANGING]
♪ Pop out the clutch
Get this thing in drive ♪
♪ Don't want to be a passenger
Who's just cruisin' by ♪
[HORN HONKING]
♪ Scratch the bumper
It doesn't matter ♪
TESSA:
But this is a story
about her reality.
Better hurry, Tessa,
the wicked witch just arrived.
[HONKING CONTINUES]
WOMAN: Tessa!
Tessa! Tessa! Tessa!
It's all right, I got this.
Thanks, Joe.
Hey, maybe she gets nicer
on vacation.
Holy crapola, Tessa!
You scuffed
my favorite bag.
I-I'm sorry, Divine,
this is a lot to carry.
Well, we're all
pitching in, Tessa.
I'll ring the cart.
Sir, could I--
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
No.
No way am I tipping
those vultures.
No! No!
[SIGHS]
Oh-oh-oh...
Be extra careful
with Sparkles, heh.
Who's a good dog?
Divine?
[MAKES BARKING SOUND]
What? Yes?
He's dead.
[GASPS]
Not in my heart, Tessa.
Mom!
The VIP Princess
package includes
a costume party,
and Reed West is performing!
Let me see!
[GASPS]
Oh!
Over here. Must you...
Even better,
we get our own private
7-minute Reed West
encounter!
We're in it for a lot more
than seven minutes, Athena!
We're here to win.
Okay, I'll-- I'll be there
in a minute.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, a pool. Athena, you need
to put on your bikini
and sit by that pool.
Okay.
Uh, not you, Olympia.
Oh, my God.
ATHENA:
These girls look like pros.
They don't have
superstar's blood
coursing
through their veins.
Remember, girls,
you're Madonna's
third cousins twice removed.
Not a lot of blood.
Blood is blood.
If I were 10 years younger,
I'd snag that role myself.
Uh-oh, Janet's here.
Her parents send her
to music camp in New York.
See you ladies
at the VIP lunch.
Ah, can't wait!
Yes.
Great.
Bianca's here too!
[SIGHS]
Lauren!
Divine!
I almost
didn't recognize you
with your new face.
Would you like
the number?
They do lipo as well.
[LAUGHS DERISIVELY]
I'd forgotten how dreadfully
witty you are.
So we're really excited
about this week.
Right, Bianca?
Sweetheart?
Darling?
Bianca, sweetheart.
[LAUREN CHUCKLES]
Yeah. So excited.
[SCOFFS]
She's a bit of a slug,
isn't she?
She's been rehearsing.
Huh?
You've only brought
one assistant.
So brave.
[LAUGHS DERISIVELY]
Oh, uh, I'm not
her assistant,
I'm her stepdaughter.
Uhh, Tessa?
Yeah?
Could you please
go get Sparkles?
Get Sparkles!
Yes, right away, Divine.
Thank you.
She's a bit sensitive
about her position
in life.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Well, it's been fascinating,
but, mm, now I'm bored.
Oh.
Tessa,
we're on the move!
Right away!
[♪♪♪]
♪ Uh-huh ♪
Oh, Reed,
I would sell
body parts for you.
Good ones.
Ugh, gross.
Stop drooling, Olympia.
Ugh, grr...
He's definitely
worth a kidney.
He looks taken.
Who's the girl?
Ugh.
Harper Halston.
The heiress.
She's so pretty.
Her family owns
Royal Lagoon Resorts.
They're holding
the audition contest.
You'd know all this
if you weren't so busy
greasing up carburetors
or whatever.
You mean my job.
Not this week, Tessa.
You're here to help
Athena and Olympia
focus on one thing:
dazzling Reed and winning
the lead role.
[SQUEALS]
One of you girls
is going to star in the musical,
win that recording contract,
and do me proud.
I named you after goddesses
for a reason.
What's
the musical?
Cinderella.
Okay, that's
kind of ironic.
You follow me.
Yes, ma'am.
DIVINE:
You are going
to love your little room.
Okay, so it's
right this way.
Okay, all right.
Ahem.
DIVINE: Whoo!
[COUGHING]
It's just like
having your own spa.
[CHUCKLES]
Right through here.
Here we go.
Nice and cozy,
under the stairs.
So I'm Harry Potter.
Exactly.
[CHUCKLES]
Now, um,
be careful of the gate,
because it locks
from the outside.
A-And don't tell anyone
you're here, okay?
Oh, I'm going to get
into so much trouble for this.
Don't worry, it's not exactly
something I'll Instagram.
Yeah.
Thanks.
[BED SQUEAKS]
[CHATTERING AND LAUGHTER]
[WHISPERING]
Olympia, stop that!
That's disgusting!
Stop it!
DIVINE:
Oh, my God, what are you doing?
Stop it!
Don't eat that!
Don't you dare
put that in your mouth!
I cannot believe you're
humiliating me this way!
[SCOFFS]
[DIVINE CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY]
Oh, dear.
Oh...
Hello, hello.
Like really ready.
I think you have this
in the bag.
Like I've never seen
such a dull group of girls.
You remember Janet?
Oh, yes, oh, Jane, hello.
It's Janet.
Oh, you dropped some--
Ooh. Ooh.
[ALL LAUGH]
Whoops.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Tsk-- Tsk-- Ah!
Ow.
Tessa.
[WOMEN VOCALIZE]
Ladies...
Thank you so much.
She's--
She's a little slow,
but you know,
she smells good,
so we keep her around.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
LAUREN:
You're so bad!
[♪♪♪]
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
FREDDIE:
Heh, hello, hello.
Welcome, VIPs.
You know,
by the looks of this crowd,
you'd think VIP stands
for "very beautiful person."
[LIGHT LAUGHTER]
I guess that'd be V.B.P.
But um, ah, thank you!
Welcome, everyone!
I'm Freddie Marks,
the director,
and you all know, heh,
pop sensation Reed West.
[WOMEN HOOT AND HOLLER]
Hi, it's lovely to be here.
I discovered Reed on YouTube,
and now I'm hoping to find
a brand new star
right here in this very room.
Harper sang
a romantic duet with Reed.
Will you be next?
Ah, now, auditions
will be held tomorrow morning.
and the show will premiere
on the very last night
of your VIP stay,
so this is
gonna be a fast-paced,
exciting adventure for
all those who make the cast,
especially one
very lucky young lady.
And the best part?
If our Cinderella impresses
the Slick Tracks record execs,
she'll be signed on the spot.
Whoo!
FREDDIE: Yeah, how about that?
FREDDIE:
All right,
so good luck, everybody,
and we'll see you all
in the morning. Thank you.
Cheers.
[♪♪♪]
[SNAPS FINGERS]
DIVINE:
Earth to Tessa...
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
Mom? Mom?
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Help. Mom, I'm drowning,
I'm drowning!
[COUGHS]
Oh, my God.
Help!
Sorry,
give me one second.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, grab this.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
TESSA:
Got it?
DIVINE:
She's so funny
when she's drowning.
It's so great.
Gently, Tessa.
[SIGHS]
Will you do my face?
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[CHUCKLES]
Am I getting it all?
Mm, yeah, just, um,
I think you missed a spot,
just right...
There?
Yeah, right there.
Was that it?
Oh, yeah.
We wouldn't want you
to get sunburned.
Okay, good, you can go now.
Okay.
Spritz.
[MAN SINGING IN DISTANCE]
♪ 'Cause we all want a friend
To call our own ♪
♪ These days get
Mighty cold sometime ♪
♪ So I guess
I'll just make a squish ♪
♪ And close my eyes ♪
♪ And I'm wishing up
On a star ♪
♪ That I'll find you
Wherever you are ♪
♪ And I just know
That special someone's ♪
♪ Out there somewhere ♪
Great song, huh?
Heh.
Yes, it's beautiful.
♪ Nobody ever wants
To be alone ♪
♪ 'Cause we all want a friend ♪
Oh, I'm Georgie, by the way.
I'm the makeup artist
for the show.
Uh, I'm Tessa, currently
an indentured servant.
But you sing too.
♪ So I guess
I'll just make this wish ♪
♪ And close my eyes ♪
I heard you humming.
Oh, heh.
No, um...
I mean, yeah, I love
music and dance,
but, um, maybe
in another life.
Too bad
we only get one.
♪ I just know
The special someone's ♪
♪ Out there somewhere ♪
Um, it was nice
to meet you.
[♪♪♪]
MAN 1: All right, we got it.
TESSA: Hey.
Hey, is that
a 500cc twin?
1950, right?
Yeah, if you say so.
Can you just--?
Yeah, we're stagehands,
not really bike people.
Turn, turn.
All right, turn.
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
TESSA:
Wow...
Wow, that's one of
Lambini's very first
real sporting
V-twin engines.
She's-- She's beautiful.
You have any idea
why one of these
sporting things won't start?
You know what,
I'd love to figure it out.
Hey, can I borrow those?
My pants?
Yeah, your overalls.
Yeah-- I mean, yeah.
Thanks. Heh.
Okay.
Yeah?
Start 'er up.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ALL CHUCKLE]
Hell yeah.
Oh, nice work, Tessa.
Oh, they got
the bike started.
I wish I was there.
You could give me a ride.
TESSA:
Uh, yeah,
the alignment was just off.
The two cylinders kind of
needed to run as one,
but it's all good now.
All right, brilliant.
Thanks, mate.
Mate.
Reedsy-boo...
Can I finish my story?
I have lunch
with Kim and Paris.
Uh, yeah, sure, sure.
Guys, thanks so much.
Freddie'll cover you.
Okay. Stupid.
[PHONE RINGING]
Oh, no.
Um, I gotta go, guys,
but I'll see you later.
Let me know
how the bike goes, 'kay?
Thanks.
Some days I've worked so hard,
my body aches
like that
of an old woman.
My face
is covered in...
cinders.
My feet--
Hey, Picasso, can you
color inside the lines?
Could you hold still?
[FLATULENCE]
Me next!
DIVINE:
All right, Sparkles,
I need your opinion
on a very important subject.
What do you think?
[TOILET FLUSHING]
Candy Yum-yum?
[MAKES BARKING SOUND]
Or Lady Danger?
[MAKES GROWLING SOUND]
Ah, you rascal, you.
All right,
Lady Danger it is.
[GASPS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[DIVINE SCREAMING]
Tessa! Save Sparkles!
Sparkles is drowning!
She's drowning!
[HAIR DRYER WHIRRING]
Don't use
too much product, Tessa.
Fluffy,
but not pretentious.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Hi. Can I...?
MAN: There you go.
Thank you.
Hey, Tessa,
come on over.
Hey.
Eddie...
Let me get this for you.
TESSA: Hey, guys.
Thank you very much.
Hi.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[CHUCKLES]
Hey.
♪ Ho! ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
Shh.
My God,
they're amazing.
♪ Hey! ♪
Biggest secret here:
The best talent makes beds
in hall's trash.
Wow.
ALL:
Oh!
[LAUGHS]
Come on, Tessa.
Let's go dance, come on.
Go! Go!
Wow, Tessa!
That's crazy, girl. Come on,
show us some more moves.
Come on,
show us your moves!
Now it's your turn, Georgie.
Don't do it.
♪ Get up on your feet ♪
♪ And get down to the beat ♪
♪ Come on, let's live it loud ♪
Whoo!
♪ Come on
Come on, come on now ♪
♪ Put on your dancing shoes ♪
♪ We got nothing to lose ♪
♪ Break all the locks
Now's your chance ♪
♪ Get out of the box
And wave your hands ♪
ALL:
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Everybody's got to move ♪
♪ What's your excuse?
Come on, do you ♪
♪ Time to play
When work is through, yeah ♪
♪ There's no excuse
Come on, do you ♪
♪ We're shakin' off the rules ♪
♪ And makin' our own rules ♪
♪ Break all the locks
Now's your chance ♪
♪ Get out of the box
And wave your hands ♪
ALL:
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Everybody's got to move ♪
♪ What's your excuse?
Come on, do you ♪
♪ Time to play
When work is through, yeah ♪
♪ What's your excuse?
Come on, do you ♪
♪ Everyone, do you ♪
♪ Everybody, keep on dancing ♪
♪ Do you ♪
♪ Keep on dancing ♪
♪ There's no excuse
Come on, do you ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey
Do you ♪
♪ Ha, do you ♪
♪ Come on, do you
Do you ♪
♪ What's your excuse?
Come on, do you ♪
♪ Do you ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Do you, do you ♪
♪ There's no excuse
Come on, do you, oh yeah ♪♪
[ALL LAUGHING]
Get back to work!
Come on!
Let's go! Move!
Why are you not auditioning
for the musical?
Thanks, Georgie,
but my stepmother
would never ever allow me
to audition.
That's it!
What?
Audition in disguise.
Okay, I'm sure-- I'm sure
you're
great with makeup
and with brushes and stuff,
but I doubt it could...
[♪♪♪]
Pout for me.
I'm not so sure
about this.
Shush, shush and shush.
Yeah, let's begin.
♪ Kick in the door no locks ♪
♪ Get on the floor
We no call the cops ♪
♪ Ladies and gentlemen
You should know ♪
♪ This is a stick-up
We steal the show ♪
♪ Now run Tiggy run run
Tiggy run run ♪
♪ Hearing that bum bum
When it come come ♪
♪ Lights in a bomb
When we in the room ♪
Bull's-eye.
♪ Oh-ohh-oh
Oh-ohh ohh-oh ♪
♪ One for the money ♪
♪ We gonna make you
Lose control ♪♪
[RECORD SCRATCHES]
Oh, hey, Georgie,
who's your friend?
You know who I am.
She's a guest, Eddie.
She's a guest.
If you need anything,
you just, you let us know.
I can sweep. Sweep your room.
All right.
Sweep, sweep rooms.
He didn't recognize me
and I've worn his coveralls.
Okay, I don't know
what that means,
but I feel vindicated.
Now you have to audition.
Georgie, look,
your makeup brushes
are like magic wands,
but I can't do this.
My family will recognize
my voice immediately.
Then disguise it.
Here we are.
It's not like,
"Ugh-ah, I'm Olympia,
blah!"
It's like,
"I'm Olympia."
"I'm here."
I'm here.
"I'm yours."
[WHISPERING]
Okay, I'm going.
Okay.
I'm gonna do this.
Okay, go.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Tess, go.
Okay.
DIVINE:
You're not listening to me.
Wow, Janet,
you look great.
And don't worry,
no one will even notice
that huge vein bulging
out of your forehead.
[SCOFFS]
Hm.
Young lady,
are you a VIP guest?
I didn't see you
at the brunch.
[IN BRITISH ACCENT]
Um, the trolley broke.
The trolley?
Yes. But it's a bloody shame
the trolley broke.
I know you
from somewhere.
No, um...
Uh, I don't--
I don't think so.
The Niedermeyer
Bar Mitzvah?
Did we Hava Nagila?
I don't think
I had that pleasure, ma'am.
Eh. You didn't
have that pleasure.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
Mm-hm.
The National Dog Show
in Philly?
[MAKES BARKING SOUNDS]
Afraid not.
Um, I'm a cat person.
[MEOWS]
[SNIFFS]
You even smell familiar.
It's vanilla.
It's my deodorant.
It's all the rage in London.
England. Ahem.
Very interesting.
Mm-hm.
All right.
Yes. Mm.
I've got my eyes on you.
[WHISPERS]
Oh, that won't be
necessary, it's okay.
Cheers!
God save the queen.
In London.
Where I'm from.
DIVINE:
Whatever. All right, Olympia...
[WHISPERS]
Oh, that was close.
[♪♪♪]
♪ I know the rain is falling ♪
♪ Don't look so sad about it ♪
♪ I know it hurts a little ♪
♪ You want to scream
And shout it ♪
♪ That's the remedy ♪
♪ So let the rhythm take you
Over and over ♪
She has a big finish!
♪ I know you're down ♪
♪ And I'm picking you up ♪
♪ I know you're strong ♪
♪ I know you're tough ♪
♪ You want to sit ♪
♪ You need to move ♪
Okay, thank you, dear. Next!
[GAGGING]
[COUGHS]
[PIANIST PLAYING
CONTEMPORARY BALLAD]
[VOICE NOT AUDIBLE]
A little louder, please.
[OPERATIC]
♪ Me-ee... ♪
[NOTE HITTING MANY PITCHES]
[SIGHS]
[DRUM AND PERCUSSION NOTES]
FREDDIE:
Next!
[FAST-PACED POP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[INTERMITTENT SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[SLOW MOVING POP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Prepare to be amazed.
[SAWING]
[NERVOUS LAUGH]
[GASPS]
♪ I said let's go, go
Take it to the top now ♪
♪ Goin' hard and we're
Never gonna stop now ♪
♪ Picture us
All a-rhyme and glow ♪
♪ But we cannot wait a second
Baby no ♪
♪ So walkin' in stilettos
In my midriff, midriff ♪
♪ Pedal to the metal in
My stick shift, stick shift ♪
♪ About to check
Some shit off my wish list ♪
♪ Gonna set it up
And no one can stop me ♪
♪ I'm gonna turn it up
Go ahead and watch me ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh yeah ♪
[PIANIST PLAYING
SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
No, no!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
[PIANIST STOPS PLAYING]
[SCOFFS]
[REED STRUMMING NOTES ON GUITAR]
MAN:
Yeah, get right up there.
Clear it out.
That'll look perfect. There
should be lighting right there.
Okay, go ahead.
[GASPS]
[STAMMERS]
What's doth ye lads fancy?
What do we doth fancy,
Freddie?
You're supposed
to come prepared, sweetie.
Right.
I just-- Just one second.
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
♪ Nobody ever
Wants to be alone ♪
♪ 'Cause we all want a friend
To call our own ♪
♪ These days get mighty cold
Sometimes ♪
♪ So I guess I'll just make
This wish and close my eyes ♪
♪ There is no place
That I won't go ♪
♪ Because for love
I will search high ♪
♪ And I'll search low ♪
♪ All things worth having
Takes a risk ♪
♪ If I got one shot ♪
♪ I hope that I don't miss ♪
♪ And I'm wishin'
Upon a star ♪
♪ That I'll find you
Wherever you are ♪
♪ And I just know that special
Someone's out there somewhere ♪
[PIANO STOPS]
[WHISPERS]
Wow.
Well, it's pretty average.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
What's your name?
Um, Cinderella.
Cinderella?
Mm-hm.
Oh. Ironic.
Just a bit.
Hm.
[CHUCKLES]
I like your top.
I've got a pair
of boxers like those.
Go London.
Patriotic, you know.
Yeah, heh.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Whereabout you from?
I can't quite find
your accent.
Oh, you can't?
Mm-mm.
That's odd. Mm...
I'm from--
It's a small farming village.
It's just north
of London.
It's called, um...
It's called
Yorkshire Puddingshire.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Yorkshire Puddingshire?
York-- Yorkshire.
Yorkshire Puddingshire, oh.
Mm-hm.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, is that near...?
Y-- Uh-huh.
It's-- It's right--
It's right near Ho--
Hogwarts shire.
Hogwarts shire, Freddie.
Yes.
I knew it.
[BOTH NERVOUSLY CHUCKLE]
Yeah. Okay.
Well, Yorkshire Puddingshire,
let me see if you can move.
You want me to dance?
Yeah, I'd love you to dance.
[POP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Ooh yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Tell me, baby
Did you like the way I move? ♪
♪ Come on,
Get your dancer on ♪
♪ You can have as much fun
As you can possibly have ♪
♪ With your pants on ♪
♪ When I look in your eyes ♪
♪ They saying chillax ♪
♪ I bet you
There's a devil inside ♪
♪ Hookin' and playin', baby ♪
♪ I hate to lose ♪
♪ So show me
On the dance floor ♪
♪ I can see you got game ♪
♪ Well, I got game ♪
♪ You better show me
By your game, come on ♪
♪ Let's get this game on ♪
♪ Come on, babe ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh, yeah ♪
♪ Who can start a fire? ♪
♪ The fire be like that ♪
Are you ready?
For what?
Whoa!
Can you salsa?
Oh. Not at all.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Catch me.
Catch you?
♪ Everything is playing
You know, it's all right ♪
♪ If you're playing
With me now, oh yeah ♪
Who the hell is she?
Uh, it's hard to say.
Why does she get to dance?
Hard to say?
She's an imposter!
She wasn't even
at the kickoff brunch!
Well, she's here now.
[DIVINE STAMMERING]
I'm so sorry, I have to go.
What? No, wait,
you're amazing. Wait.
Arrest that girl!
She's impersonating a VIP!
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
Well, I guess
the fairy tale gods have spoken.
[SCOFFS]
GEORGIE:
The way you two
danced together...
It was like a fairy tale.
I bet he's gonna pick you.
[CHUCKLES]
It doesn't matter.
You saw Divine.
She'd get me disqualified
in a heartbeat.
We'll come up with a fake name
and it'll all work out.
Georgie,
I'm really sorry.
I really-- I really
appreciate everything
you've done for me,
but...
[SIGHS]
I think it's time for me
to get back to my real life.
But thank you.
[CROWD MURMURING]
[WHISPERS]
Oh-oh, sit up straight.
Sit up straight.
[LIGHT APPLAUSE]
Well, I'd just like
to start off by saying
thank you very much
to everyone here
for auditioning today.
We're posting a cast list soon
of the secondary roles,
but...
I found my Cinderella.
[AUDIENCE GASPS]
Well, now I just need
to actually find her, heh.
Our mystery Cinderella,
she lost her dance shoe today
at the audition.
[GASPS]
Um...
It's a very special shoe.
Uh, if you're the owner
of that matching shoe,
then please come forward
by midnight tomorrow...
and the role is yours.
[AUDIENCE GASPS]
Thank you.
DIVINE:
Girls! Girls!
Out of my way! Out of my way!
DIVINE:
Excuse me! Follow me!
Try to keep up! Try to keep up!
Clear the road!
Coming through!
This one?
Nope.
This one? This one?
Nope. Nope.
This one?
Nope.
I'm not sure!
Think, Olympia.
Round up every last
little brain cell
that's in there.
Good morning.
This one? This one?
Nope. Nope.
This--
Wait. Yes.
That's-- That's the shoe flower,
that's the one.
Oh. Tessa...
You need to paint
that flower on this shoe.
[CHUCKLES]
Um, there's no point,
because if he has
the matching sneaker, then--
Nobody else knows about
the hand-painted flower.
He has to pick somebody
by midnight.
Go! Go! Go!
Okay. Okay.
[ALL SCOFF]
Guess what? "Get Loose" just
made the Billboard Hot 100!
Wow, that was fast.
See, I told you duet with
Harper
would be gold for your career.
[ALL SCREAMING]
Uh, if anybody's
interested,
the supporting cast list
has just been posted backstage.
Come on, Reed,
let's go!
Okay, I tried, but I just really
don't think this is gonna work.
What happened?
Did someone die?
Worse! Bianca got cast
as Fairy Godmother.
Janet's
the Evil Stepmother,
and all we get to play
is the...
Ugly Stepsisters!
How could they possibly think
that we should play
those mean, horrible
self-absorbed girls?!
Gosh, it just boggles
the imagination, doesn't it?
Finally.
What, did you paint it
with your toes?
As usual,
I'll take care of things.
Right, girls?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Uh, hello?
Doorbell.
[EVIL SNICKER]
DIVINE:
Olympia, sit up straight.
Athena, stop looking
so depressed.
It's from Reed West.
[ALL GASP AND SCREAM]
[MANIACAL LAUGHTER]
[PANTING]
"Reed West requests
the company of..."
No!
What is it? What's wrong?
You!
Why does he want to see you?!
[BOTH GASP]
What?
I saw you
at Reed's announcement
making gooey eyes at him.
No, it's--
That's ridic--
You plucked your eyebrows
for him, didn't you?
No, I didn't, I didn't.
It's just--
It's just some--
A big misunderstanding.
It's just a silly mistake.
Well, we'll find out, shall we?
Come with me!
DIVINE:
Girls! Girls! We're leaving!
REED:
♪ See there, staring here ♪
DIVINE:
Yeah, we're gonna get
to the bottom of this
right now, little missy,
and if you screw things up
for my girls--
Girls, try to keep up.
Oh, Reed. Reed West.
I have Tessa here.
You wanted to see her?
Oh, hang on a sec.
Oh, yes, we've been trying
to track you down.
You have?
Uh, why would you
want to see her?
Well, I-- I just need
your help.
You do?
The show kinda depends on it.
It does?
[REED STAMMERS] The mechanic
said
you were the one who got her
started yesterday.
Yeah. Yeah. I did.
I'm sorry for mistaking you
for a dude.
It's my bad.
It's okay, I'm just--
I'm just glad everything's
all cleared up now.
Right, well,
there's a--
There's like
a little clunking noise
coming from the--
From, uh--
Uh, from
the motorcycle.
From the bike.
Yeah.
Um, could you describe
the clunking?
Like a tk, tk, tk,
tk, tk, tk, tk.
Okay. Is it like
a fast tk-tk?
Like a "t-t-t-t-t"
tk, tk, tk?
Kind of.
Well, it starts off--
It starts off
like it's building.
Okay. So like "b-b-b-b-b"
tk, tk?
[OLYMPIA AND ATHENA LAUGH]
No, it's more like
a tk, tk, tk, tk.
Tk, tk, tk, tk, tk, tk.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
Like a train?
I don't know what trains
you've heard, but yeah,
it cuts out, and if
I try and do it again,
it goes,
tk, tk, tk, tk, tk, tk.
Um, yeah,
I think I know it.
Well, we just need
to get it fixed if we can,
otherwise Cinderella
won't have a pumpkin carriage.
I can try.
Wait. Wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
If I let my darling Tessa
do this for you,
you have to do
something for me.
You have to let my talented
daughters audition again.
They had an eentsy problem
the first time.
By the way,
prepare to have
your mind blown.
Uh...
Yeah, deal.
Ah!
[DIVINE LAUGHING]
Oh.
Come on, girls,
we have to practice!
Bye, Reed!
Bye.
Uh, Freddie, can we set Tessa up
in the prop room, please?
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES]
It's not--
It's not as bad
as it looks, I swear, heh.
Well, this is nothing compared
to the hot mess I just saw, heh.
I'm sure, I kind of
overheard a little bit.
Okay, so these are the parts
that I need you to get,
so that I can fix
your pumpkin carriage.
Where did you learn
to do all this?
Um, my dad was
a racecar driver.
Oh.
Yeah.
He had
his own repair shop,
so I was basically
working on cars
before I could walk.
[CHUCKLES]
Is your dad
still racing cars now?
Um, I hope so.
In heaven.
Could you pass me
the 9/16th spanner?
No.
Oh, the wrench.
Oh.
No, I don't know
what that one is.
The small,
silver thing, r--
This one?
Mm-hm.
Small silver thing here.
Right there.
You should've just said that.
Thanks, heh.
So did your dad let
Baby Tessa drive racecars too?
No.
No, I had to wait
till I was about 5 for that.
Ha, ha.
All right, wise to wait.
[PHONE RINGS WITH POP MUSIC]
Oh.
Hey.
You did it, babe!
The show sold out.
The resort too.
Heh, Dad's thrilled.
Oh, that's great.
Freddie says you haven't
cast Cinderella yet?
No, not yet.
But there's someone
we're hoping's gonna accept it.
Then make it happen,
hot stuff.
Anyway, gotta fly.
[PHONE BEEPS OFF]
Sorry, there's
a lot goin' on.
It's okay.
I'm in trouble
if this girl doesn't show.
You really think
your mystery girl's that good?
Oh, definitely.
But Royal Resorts want us
to complete casting today.
Yeah...
And if mystery girl
doesn't come forward,
then we have to pick
someone else.
I like spending time
with you.
[CHUCKLES]
I'd really like it
if you'd meet me tomorrow,
and maybe, uh,
well, you'd let me
hold your spanner.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh, my God.
I thought
he was going to be like,
all abs and attitude,
but...
he's-- He's so sweet.
Heh, someone's
crushing hard.
Oh, please, he's dating
a gorgeous celebrity heiress.
Who can't possibly hold
a candle to you.
She doesn't have to,
she has people for that.
It's okay,
it's just the way things are.
I wish...
What?
Your dad.
He made his dreams
come true, right?
Yeah.
Wouldn't he want you
to do the same?
GEORGIE:
I just hate to see
perfectly good dreams
go to waste.
[♪♪♪]
TESSA:
Okay, Dad,
I'll be brave.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[BOTH SQUEAL]
Come on!
MAN:
How much longer
is this gonna take?
All right. Move it.
FREDDIE: I don't know.
I don't know.
All right.
[SNORING]
[SIGHING AND YAWNING]
[SIGHS]
Look, she's not coming.
Can we just pick someone?
No, it's not midnight yet.
Just a few more minutes.
[TAP DANCING]
[WHISPERING]
Stop it!
So annoying.
Unbelievable.
[SIGHS]
Reed, if we don't
pick someone,
they'll cancel
my show.
Please?
All right.
Um...
Am I too late?
[AUDIENCE GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
It's her, right?
Heh, yeah.
[AUDIENCE MURMURING]
[EXHALES]
[BRITISH ACCENT]
Hello.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Cherry blossoms
were me mum's
favorite flowers.
Why did you run?
I wasn't sure I should've
auditioned at all.
Oh.
Well, you've changed
your mind?
All right, you'll be
my Cinderella?
Yes.
DIVINE:
Hold on a second!
Wait one minute!
Hold on! Hold on!
I have something to say!
This girl,
I bet she's not even
a legitimate guest.
What? That's absurd.
[MOCKING VOICE]
Oh, absurd!
Of course I'm...
DIVINE: Ohh...
...a guest
REED: Well, what's your name?
My name?
Hm, yes.
Right, because everyone--
Everyone has a name,
right?
Spit it out.
[MOCKING COUGHS]
Mm-hm.
Um, hm...
The um...
The-- See, the name
that my mother
gave me was...
Bella!
Bella.
TESSA: Bella Buckingham.
Bella Snow!
GEORGIE: Bella Buckingham?
It's Bella
Buckingham Snow.
Bel-- Bella Snow,
for short.
It's good to see you!
I was just
at your mom's castle.
In-in Yorkshire
Puddingshire, how lovely, heh!
[GEORGIE AND TESSA LAUGH]
Yep, Bella Snow, VIP.
She's legit.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
DIVINE:
Okay, all right. All right.
[WHISPERING]
I'm on to you!
You and your silly sneakers
had better watch your step!
Okay then, read this,
check out the links,
learn the routines,
start rehearsal
in the morning.
All right, heh.
[DIVINE MAKES BARKING NOISE]
No! No carbs for you!
You're getting too fat.
Here's the tablet
you requested.
All right. Sit down,
I want you to Google something.
Okay, what do you
want me to Google?
ATHENA:
Google "Bella Snow."
Snow.
Bella Snow.
Snow, like the stuff
that falls from the sky.
B-E-L-- Just give that to me.
Let me do it.
You're so slow.
DIVINE:
You do it. She's too slow.
Okay...
Okay, here's one.
Bella Snow,
a dentist in New Jersey.
[DIVINE AND OLYMPIA LAUGH]
That's not her.
That girl is as brainless
as they come.
Okay, I found
a British Bella Snow,
who died a hundred years ago.
This is pointless.
She doesn't exist!
I knew it!
She's an imposter!
I want you to follow her
after rehearsal,
and find out who she is.
Me?
Oh, uh, I'll go too.
Can I go?
Shh! Shh!
Shh!
Shh-shh! Shh!
I'm gonna go make sure
the chef
has your suggestions for dinner.
Oh, all right.
And you know, I want
the spritzing station
by the cabana today.
Got it.
I love to be spritzed.
Just go with what you're
feeling at the time.
And don't decide
beforehand.
Just let it be whatever you're
feeling in the moment, okay?
MAN 1: Cool.
FREDDIE: Yeah? Cool.
Oh, good, you're here.
Okay, so, um, we wanna do
Cinderella's opening song.
You're ready, right?
Okay, great, let's give
her some space, folks.
Right, the song's about a girl
who lives a difficult life,
filled with loss,
who struggles to find the
courage to go after her
dreams.
Try to imagine what that
might be like, okay?
I can try.
FREDDIE:
Okay, places, everybody.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
IN DISTANCE]
♪ I've never been one ♪
♪ To step out of
My comfort zone ♪
♪ Whenever I try ♪
♪ I'm afraid to just let go ♪
♪ I've never been one ♪
♪ To break free ♪
♪ 'Cause I've always cared
What everyone thinks ♪
♪ Of me ♪
♪ Don't know why I run ♪
♪ Don't know why I hide ♪
♪ Never let them know
What I feel inside ♪
♪ Don't know why I'm scared ♪
♪ Just to take a chance ♪
♪ When I'm just standing here ♪
♪ Like a bird
I'm free to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings
And find my life ♪
♪ Like a bird
I'm up so high ♪
♪ Out of the cage
It's my time to shine ♪
♪ Like a bird
I'm free to fly ♪
♪ So tell me, tell me ♪
♪ Why don't I? ♪
[PEOPLE CLAP, WHOOP]
We definitely found
our girl.
Okay.
Seventeen.
Arms up. Up, up, up.
I'm sorry.
Hmm.
Sorry.
Whoo!
You got a waist
like a little hummingbird.
I'll be back.
Cheers.
[EXHALES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Bella.
[CHUCKLING]
Georgie.
Oh, look at you,
all princessy!
[EXHALES]
TESSA:
For the first time,
I feel like...
maybe I can do this.
Like, for real.
Hi!
ATHENA [WHISPERS]: Come on!
Ugh, my God,
my stepsisters are waiting
to follow me outside.
We'll go out the back.
They won't expect it.
You sure?
Mm-hm.
Okay. I'm gonna go. Bye.
Okay.
Where is she?
[SCOFFS]
[GASPS]
Come on!
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
Okay. You go that way.
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
Gotcha!
[GASPS]
[GASPS, GROANS]
What?
Who are you?
Gotcha!
Olympia!
Oh, it's just such a--
Such a delight to see you
here.
It is?
Would you be so kind as to
pass me that suntan lotion
over there too?
We Brits, we just crisp
so easily.
Oh, do you mind?
I can't reach.
Thank you.
So tell me, Olympia,
was it hard to get all those
scarves in your mouth?
Oh, I had to train my cheeks
for weeks.
Did you?
Do you wanna see?
Sure.
That's a lot of grapes.
Do you know what would be
lovely? Some lemonade.
Mm. And snacks.
Yes, and snacks.
I can get 'em!
Oh, you could.
Mm-hm.
Oh, that's absolutely perfect.
Okay.
Thank you. I'll be
just right here waiting,
right here, won't move.
She's so nice.
And smart.
Oh.
But then she disappeared
before I could give her
her snacks.
Ugh. You got played,
Olympia.
You're just jealous
because Bella's head
is prettier than yours.
Where have you been?
I was just picking up
the dresses you ordered.
[BOTH GASP]
Oh!
Are these for
the Costume Ball?
We're going as Cinderellas.
[SQUEALS]
Okay.
[CHUCKLES, SQUEALS]
Abracadabra!
Heh, heh, just...
that's what a magician says.
Uh, so this
is your wand.
It's very simple to use.
Just demonstrate for you.
Uh, Gino, could you step into
Cinderella's position, please?
Yeah.
So all you do is...
twirl.
[CHUCKLES]
See?
Uh, it's so easy.
Just a flick of the wrist.
Here, go ahead.
Get a feel for it,
and, uh, let me know
if you have any questions.
Sorry.
She's ridiculous.
What were you thinking
getting Bianca
and her stepsisters
in the show?
Olympia, stop it. Gross.
FREDDIE:
We have no choice.
The VIP package guarantees
them supporting roles.
[SCOFFS]
Don't worry.
It'll be fine.
I can get a great performance
out of anybody.
These wings
are so heavy.
She's gonna be great.
FREDDIE:
So it's four beats
in the hips.
Pop! Pop!
Ba-dap-pow!
MAN: All right.
BOTH: Pop! Pop! Ba-dap-pow!
Oh, uh, Bella's here,
so let's rehearse the
shoe-fitting scene, please.
[GROANS]
Yes, that's what we're gonna do.
Freddie,
can you run the show
without me for a little bit?
What? Why?
Where are you going?
To fix Cinderella's
pumpkin carriage.
Can't do the show without it,
right?
Yeah, uh...
I guess I'll stand in.
Heh.
If Tessa's not there,
he'll think she's a flake
or doesn't care.
You can't be in
two places at once.
Meet me in Make-up with
coveralls and a cap, okay?
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
[♪♪♪]
How are you gonna pull this off?
Great question.
I think I'll get Reed started,
then tell him I have to go.
I'll just meet you back here
for the Bella wig.
You work your magic
with your magic make-up hands.
We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Okay. Oh.
Wait. Okay.
Do you need a brush?
Oh, no, that's okay.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Ew. Ew.
Hat.
Here.
You look good.
Okay.
Oh.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Okay.
Oh, thank God.
I thought you forgot.
No, I, uh... It just takes
a little time to look this hot.
[GRUNTS]
Sorry.
I got those parts
that you asked for.
I don't know--
Oh, wow.
That's--
That's amazing.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Heh, um...
Wow, I'm surprised you got
these parts so quickly.
Yeah, well, the perks
of being a pop star.
Must be nice.
Not really.
But nobody should have to
listen to pop star problems.
Like getting
everything you could want,
including
awesome bike parts?
Yeah...
Not exactly.
Or, like, um...
not being able to follow
your heart, maybe.
Uh...
I heard those songs that
you wrote for the musical.
They're really good.
Beautiful.
Really?
Honestly?
Honestly.
That's the real you, right?
Well, Freddie just thinks
I need to stick to my brand
until my career reaches
the next level.
Then I can do
whatever I want.
Freddie could be wrong.
Yes, it's just that he's been
right about everything else.
Mm. Like I said,
pop star problems.
Well, they're safe
with me.
Yeah, I believe
they are.
Yeah, you're gonna need that.
Yeah.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[♪♪♪]
[WHISPERS]
Come on!
Uh-- Oh, uh, just...
Will you just tighten
these bolts really quick
and, um, finish
putting on the belt.
And I will be--
I'll be right back.
I've gotta go
check on some things.
You're gonna come back?
I can't do this without you.
Yes. Of course,
I'll be back.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, God.
MAN: Bella...
There you go.
You're supposed to
make a noise there.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[OBJECT CLATTERS]
[PANTING]
Am I too late to try on
the slipper?
Every maiden in the land
is granted the opportunity.
Could that
be her?
Ow.
Could that be her?
The lass that I have waited
my whole life for? Come!
Come!
Please, present your foot.
What?
Your mole
switched cheeks.
Oh, it's...
It happens to
all the Snow women.
We just, ahem, we just
don't like to talk about it.
Okay. Uh...
[WHISPERING]
Okay, yeah,
bring your foot up.
Good. And...
A perfect fit!
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Okay, and now we get up,
we come up,
and get ready for
the spin.
I have found you,
my princess!
And you shall never
wear rags again!
Come, come!
Come on.
Come, come, come.
Never fear,
your fairy godmother is here.
Let others see you
as I do.
Twirl.
Come on.
Flick the wrist,
like I showed you--
Twirl!
[FREDDIE YELPS]
[SCREAMS]
For cryin' out loud, people!
Aah! Fix this! Please!
And let's take it
from the top.
Bella...
Now where is she?
So you put the mole
in the wrong s--
Georgie?
Okay. Here we go.
[GRUNTS]
Oh!
[PANTING]
Georgie, what are--
What are you doing here?
Well, Tessa...
[SIGHS]
Reed was looking for you
so I offered to help.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Um, right, right.
I will, um...
I, Tessa, will take it
from here.
Thank you, Georgie.
You're welcome.
Hi.
[SIGHS] Sorry.
Oh.
Are you okay?
You look a little bit flushed.
[EXHALING]
Oh.
Sorry.
Ah, you're okay.
Um...
Have you seen Bella?
She's AWOL.
Uh, no.
No, she'll be back. She promised
not to disappear again.
Yeah, right.
So much for promises.
Um, where was I?
Oh...
You know what, I--
I think I, uh,
I just saw Bella,
And I think I should probably
just go check on her
for Freddie.
No, don't go,
please. I've got to go
and perform in a minute.
Um, this will just take a
second. I'll be right back.
[♪♪♪]
There you are!
Divine! Hi!
Oh, I know
what you were doing.
You do? Oh.
Yes.
These eyes see
everything.
They do.
Hmm.
Ooh, I know you have
your own little fantasies
about being up on stage,
but, heh,
lurking around the VIP area
of Cinderella is just...
sad, and frankly,
a little creepy.
Right. Yeah. Of course.
Um, I'm so sorry.
No more creeping. Understood.
Oh, good.
Now, where
are those gowns?
Uh--
The gowns!
Oh, the gowns!
Where are the gowns?
The gowns. I was about
to pick the gowns up,
actually.
You could come with,
unless, of course,
you don't wanna be seen in,
you know, the service area.
[BOTH LAUGH UNCOMFORTABLY]
Have them in the suite
in five minutes.
You need to help us
get dressed.
Yes, of course, heh.
[SIGHS]
Sorry I'm late. I had
to find more contacts.
It's okay.
Is this almost over?
No. Now I need to be
in three places at once.
Now that's what I call
star power.
Twirl, girls,
twirl for Sparkles.
[IMITATES DOG YIPPING]
Oh, Tessa.
I have something
for you.
For me?
I didn't forget you, Tessa.
There you go.
You can't go to a costume ball
without a costume.
Wow. Thank you, Divine.
You're so welcome.
[GRUNTS, SQUEALS]
[♪♪♪]
♪ Oh, we gonna give 'em
Oh, we gonna give 'em ♪
♪ We gonna give 'em ♪
♪ S-somethin' somethin'
Somethin' to talk about ♪
♪ We gonna give 'em
Oh, we gonna give 'em ♪
♪ Oh, we gonna give 'em
We gonna give 'em ♪
♪ S-somethin' somethin' ♪
♪ Somethin' to talk about ♪
♪ Walk in the door
Rockin' Gucci and that Prada ♪
♪ Your homeboys
They tryin' to holler... ♪
All right, girls.
Let the dazzling begin.
[CHUCKLES]
Hmm.
Stand up straight.
Smile.
Chest forward.
Outta my way, big baby!
Ha-ha-ha!
[TOY SQUEAKS]
[SIGHS]
♪ And we gonna give 'em ♪
Oh, there's a lot
of Cinderellas here.
You girls, in the back.
Hello.
[CHEERING]
On behalf of the Halstons
and Royal Lagoons Resorts,
welcome to
the VIP Costume Ball!
[CHEERING]
Whoo!
First,
one little question.
Is anyone in this room
ready to get loose?
[CHEERING]
Okay. Play the music.
[UPBEAT HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Yeah, uh-huh ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ I see you there
Staring here ♪
♪ Make a move
Why are you scared? ♪
♪ Push yourself
Forget the clock ♪
♪ We got all night
Then still wake up ♪
♪ Let down your hair
For just one night ♪
♪ Come on, now
Why are you still shy? ♪
♪ I see you there
Staring here ♪
♪ Make a move ♪
♪ Come on, baby
Get loose, loose ♪
♪ Let it go ♪
♪ Get loose, loose
On the floor ♪
Have some fun ♪
♪ The night has just begun ♪
♪ Come on, baby
Get loose, loose ♪
♪ Let it go ♪
♪ Get loose, loose
On the floor ♪
Have some fun ♪
[UPBEAT HIP-HOP MUSIC CONTINUES]
Interesting choice
of costume.
I'm a penguin.
Yes, you are.
Can you sneak away?
Uh, so we can, uh,
finish the bike.
I'll waddle out somehow.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
OLYMPIA: Tessa?
Yeah?
My hair broke.
You have to help me
put it back together.
[CHUCKLES]
Five minutes.
TESSA:
How's your mystery girl
working out for you?
She's talented, but...
she's flaky.
Oh, I'm sure
she has her reasons.
Yeah.
Maybe I'd just prefer
someone I can trust.
Someone who's funny.
Likes to laugh.
Smart, of course.
Smarter than me,
probably.
Who's amazingly cute.
And waddles.
[GIGGLES]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Um...
I think that should do it.
You wanna try
and start her up?
No,
you take the honors.
[MOTOR REVVING]
Oh!
[CHUCKLES]
You did it!
We did it.
We totally did it.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[♪♪♪]
What about Harper?
FREDDIE:
There you are!
You're supposed to be meeting
with the Halstons right now.
Uh? Oh, yeah.
Um, I lost track of time.
Can you give me one minute?
Oh, you need a minute?
By all means, yeah,
take all the--
No, you can't have
a minute!
[FREDDIE SIGHS]
We don't keep the big money
waiting, Reed.
I'll call you later.
FREDDIE:
Let's go. Let's go.
TESSA:
Freddie?
The-- The Halstons...
Um, will Harper be there?
Yes, she's flying out
to surprise Reed.
I arranged it.
So they're--
They're together.
Oh, Tessa.
[SIGHS]
I know it must be a rush
being around a guy like Reed.
I mean, he's about to
become a huge star--
I couldn't care less
about that.
--which is exactly why Harper
is so right for him.
Look, I don't know what Reed
told you,
but I'm pretty sure he's gonna
propose by the end of the month.
What?
I'm sorry, Tessa.
Really.
I'm sorry.
TESSA:
How could I have
been so stupid?
Well, I'm done.
I'm done with the show.
I'm done with Reed.
Definitely done with Bella Snow.
The show can't
go on without Bella.
He's resourceful.
He'll figure something out.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Unh. Speaking of...
Look, this is about you.
Did you become Bella Snow
to win a boy?
No. No, I became
Bella Snow because I was--
You were following
your dream.
Freddie was a real
wake-up call, Georgie.
I'm nobody. With just enough
talent to delude myself.
Oh, Tessa,
it's your decision.
But if you give up now,
you'll always wonder,
to your dying day,
what if?
God, I miss you.
I wish you were here, Dad.
[GASPING]
Well,
not exactly here.
What would you do
if you were me?
["WHY DON'T I" PLAYING]
♪ I've never been one ♪
♪ To step out
Of my comfort zone ♪
♪ Whenever I try
I'm afraid to just let go ♪
♪ Don't know why
I run ♪
♪ Don't know why I hide
Never let them know ♪
♪ What I feel inside ♪
♪ Don't know why
I'm scared ♪
♪ Just to take a chance ♪
♪ Well,
I'm still standing here ♪
♪ I've never been one ♪
♪ To break free ♪
♪ 'Cause I've always cared
What everyone thinks of me ♪
♪ Don't know why
I run ♪
♪ Don't know why I hide
Never let them know ♪
♪ What I feel inside ♪
♪ I don't want to settle
Don't want to run ♪
♪ This is not
Where I belong ♪
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
Well done.
[GASPS]
It's just-- It's hard to be
Cinderella when I know
my prince charming is in love
with someone else.
Get a grip. And focus
on what's important.
[SIGHS]
Yeah, you're right.
Go back out there and
show 'em who are you.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Do you get what's going on?
No.
[GROANS]
[WALTZ PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[SHUDDERS]
That's right.
We're mean.
We don't like you.
You're a hardball.
[PANTS]
[♪♪♪]
[SNEEZES]
Georgie?
Georg--
[GASPING]
Divine.
Cheerio, "Bella."
[LAUGHS]
[SNIFFS]
I knew you smelled
like cookies.
Did you really think you
could get away with this?
Athena has the blood of a star
running through her veins,
and she will take
her rightful place.
Divine, please don't do this.
"Please don't do this, Divine."
[LAUGHING]
Too-da-loo. Ha, ha.
Divine, no. No, no, no, no.
No, Divine, please!
[♪♪♪]
Divine!
Please,
can someone hear me?
[PANTING]
Come on, think, Tessa, think.
REED:
Georgie, is Tessa all right?
She's not answering
my calls or texts.
If you really care,
why don't you ask Freddie?
[♪♪♪]
[VENT RUMBLING]
[GRUNTS]
She's the one.
But how do we find her,
my prince?
We must search the land
to find the lovely maiden
whose delicate foot
fits this glass slipper.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
♪ I know they say
That sometimes ♪
♪ That one size fits all ♪
♪ But there's
Only one girl in here ♪
♪ That's fit to be
The belle of the ball ♪
♪ There can only be one ♪
♪ So I'm looking for
The right one ♪
♪ Before the end
Of the night, sir ♪
♪ I need every girl
To gather around ♪
♪ Put your left in the crown
Stick out the right one ♪
♪ 'Cause all I need is you
To slip, slip on slide 'em on ♪
♪ 'Cause we don't really
Have much time, come on ♪
♪ When the clock hits 12
Major fail ♪
♪ Three, two, one
Okay, now ♪
♪ Eeny, meeny, miny, moe ♪
♪ Which girl's the one
Man, I don't know ♪
♪ Eeny, meeny, miny, moe ♪
♪ Who's got the foot
That'll rock the sole ♪
♪ Well, if the shoe fits
Then go put it on ♪
♪ Go put it on ♪
♪ Well, if the shoe fits
Then go put it on ♪
♪ Go put it on ♪
♪ Well, if the shoe fits you
You know what to do ♪
♪ Put it on ♪
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
Why isn't Bella
in position?
I don't know. I've been
waiting to dress her in--
Where's her costume?
Oh, oh.
[GROANS]
What is wrong with you?
Why are you so fat?
It's so small.
Let me try.
[ALL MUTTERING]
Olympia, keep watch!
[BOTH MUTTERING]
Why can't
I be Cinderella?
Because Olympia!
You're just not good enough!
Ow. Aah!
[MUTTERING]
Wait, Mom. Who's going
to play my part?
[GASPING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[KNOCKING]
Welcome to our humble home.
His highness
requests the presence
of all the ladies
of the house.
My two daughters and I are--
Where's your sister,
dear?
Who cares?
Maybe she's dead.
[AUDIENCE MUTTERING]
No, I remember.
She's in her room.
BOTH:
Aah!
[AUDIENCE CHUCKLES]
Silly me. How could I forget?
I meant she's far,
far away in Detroit.
Wait! Hold on, hold on.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
Here I am, Mother!
[ALL CONTINUE LAUGHING]
Just keep going!
And find Bella!
...Detroit, when it's Royal
Try-on-a-Glass-Shoe Day?
[LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GASPING]
Why waste your princely time
on ground beef
when you could
have filet mignon?
[ROARS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Don't be afraid.
I don't bite.
Well, maybe a little bit
here and there.
[ALL CONTINUE LAUGHING]
Actually,
I'm just all cuddles.
Go ahead,
ask my sister.
That doesn't appear
to be an option.
Huh?
[ALL LAUGHING]
What is happening out there?
[PANTING]
I'll show Mom I'm good enough!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Stop it!
You're ruining everything!
Aah, you evil girl,
come back here!
[LAUGHING]
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
[CLEARING THROAT]
Alas,
it does not fit.
Are you sure, Prince?
Really, really sure.
Cram it in.
Okay, I don't care,
just do it.
Uh, excuse me, I must
go feed the horses.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
TESSA:
Hello, guy.
Okay. So I'm kind of
in a situation right now.
And you gotta tell me
which way to go, sugar,
that way or this way?
[SQUEAKING]
Oh, okay. Here we go.
No, I don't care. We're
not gonna stop the show.
Freddie.
[GRUNTS]
Just do it,
do it!
What are you doing?
I need you out there!
First tell me what
you said to Tessa.
Tessa? Reed,
the show's a mess.
I can't find Bella--
What are they doing?
I don't know and I don't care.
This is important.
There you are,
Prince dear.
[LAUGHS]
Get out here
or I will cut you!
What did you say to her?
Just tell me.
Go! Out!
[♪♪♪]
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
[AUDIENCE CONTINUES LAUGHING]
Right, if there are
no other ladies in the house,
then we must
take our leave.
Unless, hark, do you
hear something?
[AUDIENCE CHUCKLES]
Um, maybe?
I'm sure I must
have heard a noise!
[AUDIENCE CONTINUES LAUGHING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Ow. Ow. Really?
[GASPING]
[RATTLING]
[YELLING]
Am I too late
to try on the slipper?
[YELLING]
[MUTTERING]
[♪♪♪]
Oh, hello. Am I too late
to try on--
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[YELLS]
Am I too late to try
on the slipper?
Oh, my God! What has gotten
in to you?
Stop it, no!
I'm not going
back out there
until you tell me
what you said to Tessa.
No!
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
[CAST YELLING]
Okay. I may have
said something
about you and Harper
getting engaged.
That's all.
Why, Freddie?
Why would you say that to Tessa?
Guys, cover your mic.
Hold on, everybody, get ready
for the new Cinderella.
[CAST YELLING]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
FREDDIE:
You're on the verge of stardom.
Reed,
I did it for you.
I know you mean well,
Freddie,
but you do not get
to make those calls for me.
Harper's just a friend,
I don't like her that way.
[CAST YELLING]
No!
Tessa, I mean, she's sweet,
but what's the big deal?
REED [OVER PA]:
The big deal is,
for the first time in my life,
I think I'm in love!
[GASPS]
[ALL GASPING]
[SHATTERS]
AUDIENCE: Oh!
[AUDIENCE MURMURING]
TESSA:
♪ Nobody ever wants
To be alone ♪
♪ 'Cause we all want
A friend to call our own ♪
[AUDIENCE MURMURING]
Bella?
[♪♪♪]
Am I too late
to try on the slipper?
Tessa?
You're Cinderella?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
who I really was.
I never thought
that a prince like you
could ever love girl like me.
Not as sorry as I am,
to have caused you any pain.
My advisor, Frederico
spoke not the truth
of my impending nuptials.
Freddie totally lied about me
getting married to Harper.
I heard.
Sound travels quite well
in this kingdom.
Please, try on
the glass slipper.
I'd love to.
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS, THEN LAUGHS]
You know what? I don't
need a shoe to tell me
what I really
feel in my heart.
You're the one.
[CLAPPING]
Stop it. Stop it.
Stop it!
Stop it,
you're disgusting.
[CLAPPING]
Never fear, your fairy
godmother is here.
Let the world
see you as I do.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
Twirl.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
Yes! Come on.
Your fairy godmother
does great work.
She really does.
["WHY DON'T I" PLAYING]
♪ I've never been one ♪
♪ To step out
Of my comfort zone ♪
♪ Whenever I try
I'm afraid to just let go ♪
♪ Don't know why
I run ♪
♪ Don't know why I hide
Never let them know ♪
♪ What I feel inside ♪
♪ I don't want to settle
Don't want to run ♪
♪ This is not ♪
♪ Where I belong ♪
♪ Like a bird
I need to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings
And find my life ♪
♪ Like a bird
I'm up so high ♪
♪ Out of the cage
It's my time to shine ♪
♪ It's my time to shine ♪
♪ Like a bird
I'm free to fly ♪
♪ So tell me, tell me
Why don't I? ♪
♪ Like a bird
Free to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings
Find my life ♪
♪ Like a bird
Up so high ♪
♪ Out the cage
It's time to shine ♪
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
♪ Spread my wings
Find my life ♪
♪ Like a bird
Up so high ♪
♪ Out the cage
It's time to shine ♪
♪ Like a bird
Up so high ♪
♪ Out the cage
It's time to shine ♪
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
♪ Oh, ah ♪
Call me.
Thank you.
That was incredible.
Hi.
I'm so proud of you.
Georgie, I don't know
how to thank you.
You don't have to.
I thought you might
need this.
You're the best.
What would I do without you?
Sorry, buddy. I messed up.
But if you don't want me
to be your manager anymore,
I'll understand.
No, of course I do.
Plus, you may
even get the chance
to work with
a talented new star.
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
Hey, charming,
let's bounce.
♪ Found my life ♪
♪ Yeah... ♪
Aah, Tessa, sweetie,
we did it.
[LAUGHING]
I know I can't
take all the credit, but...
it certainly wouldn't have
happened without me, right?
Divine, you've been
the best evil stepmother
a girl could ever ask for,
but, uh--
Thank you.
I think it's definitely
time for us to part ways.
Call me.
[GRUNTS]
So?
Where do you wanna go?
♪ Time to shine... ♪
Everywhere.
TESSA:
At some point,
we all come across
an exciting opportunity,
a new path that might
scare us. My advice?
Pop the clutch, hit the road
and make your
happily-ever-after come true.
♪ Hey, yeah
Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Working all day
Gonna do my thing ♪
♪ That's what you make
You're in the travel seat ♪
♪ Rev your engine
Crank the ignition ♪
♪ Give me the key
Don't need your permission ♪
♪ Mama always told me ♪
♪ There's nothing
In this life to see ♪
♪ You're gonna miss me
Zero to sixty ♪
♪ Kicking it into gear ♪
♪ I'm in control
I'm behind the wheel ♪
♪ And I'm gonna steer
Where I wanna steer ♪
♪ I'm in control
I'm behind the wheel ♪
♪ And I'm gonna steer
Where I'm gonna steer ♪
♪ Go full throttle ♪
♪ Go full throttle
Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Go full throttle ♪
♪ Go full throttle
Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Living, living
Living ♪
♪ Living
Living, living ♪
♪ Nothing to fear ♪
♪ Put yourself in gear ♪
♪ Go full throttle ♪
♪ Go full throttle
Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ I know that rain
Is falling ♪
♪ Don't look
So sad about it ♪
♪ I know
It hurts a little ♪
♪ You wanna
Scream and shout ♪
♪ I got the remedy ♪
♪ Just let the rhythm
Take you over and over ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ I know you're down ♪
♪ Let me pick you up ♪
♪ I know you're strong ♪
♪ I know you're tough ♪
♪ You wanna sit ♪
♪ You need to move ♪
♪ Let me show you how to do it
Feel the music ♪
♪ Hey, you gotta clap
When you're happy ♪
♪ Clap when you're sad ♪
♪ Clap when your day is good
Or when it's going bad ♪
♪ Don't think too much
About it ♪
♪ Just keep your head
In the sky ♪
♪ Now don't it feel good
To say, "Hey" ♪
♪ Clap when you're happy ♪
♪ Clap when you're sad ♪
♪ Clap when your day is good
Or when it's going bad ♪
♪ Don't think too much
About it ♪
♪ Just keep your head
In the sky ♪
♪ Now don't it feel good
To say, "Hey" ♪
♪ I got a new solution
To all of this confusion ♪
♪ You'll feel so glad
You made it ♪
♪ Don't make it
Complicated ♪
♪ This is a brand new day ♪
♪ Just let the music
Take you over and over ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ I know you're down ♪
♪ Let me pick you up ♪
♪ I know you're strong ♪
♪ I know you're tough ♪
♪ You wanna sit ♪
♪ You need to move ♪
♪ Let me show you how to do it
Feel the music ♪
♪ Hey, you gotta clap
When you're happy ♪
♪ Clap when you're sad ♪
♪ Clap when your day is good
Or when it's going bad ♪
♪ Don't think too much
About it ♪
♪ Just keep your head
In the sky ♪
♪ Now don't it feel good
To say, "Hey" ♪
♪ Clap when you're happy ♪
♪ Clap when you're sad ♪
♪ Clap when your day is good
Or when it's going bad ♪
♪ Don't think too much
About it ♪
♪ Just keep your head
In the sky ♪
♪ Now don't it feel good
To say, "Hey" ♪
♪ Clap when you're happy ♪
♪ Clap when you're sad ♪
♪ Clap when your day is good
Or when it's going bad ♪
♪ Don't think too much
About it ♪
♪ Just keep your head
In the sky ♪
♪ Now don't it feel good
To say... ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
Ha, sorry.
[CREW LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]